{
    "questions": [
        {
            "type" : "text",
            "question" : "What popular saying is this?",
            "emojis" : "❓ 🔪 🐈",
            "answers" : [
                {
                    "answerA" : "",
                    "answerB" : "",
                    "answerC" : ""
                }
            ],
            "answer" : "curiosity killed the cat"
        },
        {
            "type" : "multi",
            "question" : "What emoji is this?",
            "emojis" : "🧳",
            "answers" : [
                {
                    "answerA" : "breifcase",
                    "answerB" : "luggage",
                    "answerC" : "suitcase"
                }
            ],
            "answer" : "b"
        },
        {
            "type" : "multi",
            "question" : "What emoji is this?",
            "emojis" : "⚙️",
            "answers" : [
                {
                    "answerA" : "gear",
                    "answerB" : "cog",
                    "answerC" : "wheel"
                }
            ],
            "answer" : "a"
        },
        {
            "type" : "multi",
            "question" : "What emoji is this?",
            "emojis" : "⚗️",
            "answers" : [
                {
                    "answerA" : "flask",
                    "answerB" : "beaker",
                    "answerC" : "alembic"
                }
            ],
            "answer" : "c"
        },
        {
            "type" : "text",
            "question" : "What movie is this?",
            "emojis" : "🌍🦧🦍",
            "answers" : [
                {
                    "answerA" : "",
                    "answerB" : "",
                    "answerC" : ""
                }
            ],
            "answer" : "planet of the apes"
        },
        {
            "type" : "text",
            "question" : "What movie is this?",
            "emojis" : "🐍🐅📖",
            "answers" : [
                {
                    "answerA" : "",
                    "answerB" : "",
                    "answerC" : ""
                }
            ],
            "answer" : "the jungle book"
        },
        {
            "type" : "text",
            "question" : "What movie is this?",
            "emojis" : "📞💀🔪",
            "answers" : [
                {
                    "answerA" : "",
                    "answerB" : "",
                    "answerC" : ""
                }
            ],
            "answer" : "scream"
        },
        {
            "type" : "text",
            "question" : "What does this depict?",
            "emojis" : "💸 🤗",
            "answers" : [
                {
                    "answerA" : "",
                    "answerB" : "",
                    "answerC" : ""
                }
            ],
            "answer" : "paypal"
        },
        {
            "type" : "multi",
            "question" : "What emoji is this?",
            "emojis" : "👹",
            "answers" : [
                {
                    "answerA" : "devil",
                    "answerB" : "ogre",
                    "answerC" : "jester"
                }
            ],
            "answer" : "b"
        },
        {
            "type" : "multi",
            "question" : "What emoji is this?",
            "emojis" : "🐽",
            "answers" : [
                {
                    "answerA" : "pig snout",
                    "answerB" : "pig nose",
                    "answerC" : "animal snout"
                }
            ],
            "answer" : "b"
        },
        {
            "type" : "text",
            "question" : "What movie is this?",
            "emojis" : "🐳➡️🌊",
            "answers" : [
                {
                    "answerA" : "",
                    "answerB" : "",
                    "answerC" : ""
                }
            ],
            "answer" : "free willy"
        },
        {
            "type" : "text",
            "question" : "What movie is this?",
            "emojis" : "✏️📓👩‍❤️‍👨",
            "answers" : [
                {
                    "answerA" : "",
                    "answerB" : "",
                    "answerC" : ""
                }
            ],
            "answer" : "the notebook"
        },
        {
            "type" : "text",
            "question" : "What movie is this?",
            "emojis" : "🦁🤴",
            "answers" : [
                {
                    "answerA" : "",
                    "answerB" : "",
                    "answerC" : ""
                }
            ],
            "answer" : "the lion king"
        },
        {
            "type" : "text",
            "question" : "What movie is this?",
            "emojis" : "🎈👴🏠",
            "answers" : [
                {
                    "answerA" : "",
                    "answerB" : "",
                    "answerC" : ""
                }
            ],
            "answer" : "up"
        },
        {
            "type" : "text",
            "question" : "What movie series is this?",
            "emojis" : "🤵🍸🔫",
            "answers" : [
                {
                    "answerA" : "",
                    "answerB" : "",
                    "answerC" : ""
                }
            ],
            "answer" : "james bond"
        },
        {
            "type" : "text",
            "question" : "What movie is this?",
            "emojis" : "🏃‍♂️ 🌲🌳 🏃‍♂️",
            "answers" : [
                {
                    "answerA" : "",
                    "answerB" : "",
                    "answerC" : ""
                }
            ],
            "answer" : "forest gump"
        },
        {
            "type" : "text",
            "question" : "What movie series is this?",
            "emojis" : "🦇🃏",
            "answers" : [
                {
                    "answerA" : "",
                    "answerB" : "",
                    "answerC" : ""
                }
            ],
            "answer" : "batman"
        },
        {
            "type" : "text",
            "question" : "What movie series is this?",
            "emojis" : "👩🧛🐺",
            "answers" : [
                {
                    "answerA" : "",
                    "answerB" : "",
                    "answerC" : ""
                }
            ],
            "answer" : "twilight"
        },
        {
            "type" : "text",
            "question" : "What movie is this?",
            "emojis" : "❄️🛳👩‍❤️‍👨🚪",
            "answers" : [
                {
                    "answerA" : "",
                    "answerB" : "",
                    "answerC" : ""
                }
            ],
            "answer" : "titanic"
        },
        {
            "type" : "multi",
            "question" : "What emoji is this?",
            "emojis" : "🌓",
            "answers" : [
                {
                    "answerA" : "last quarter moon",
                    "answerB" : "half moon",
                    "answerC" : "first quarter moon"
                }
            ],
            "answer" : "c"
        },
        {
            "type" : "multi",
            "question" : "What emoji is this?",
            "emojis" : "🫦",
            "answers" : [
                {
                    "answerA" : "lip bite",
                    "answerB" : "lip biting",
                    "answerC" : "biting lip"
                }
            ],
            "answer" : "c"
        },
        {
            "type" : "multi",
            "question" : "What emoji is this?",
            "emojis" : "🦠",
            "answers" : [
                {
                    "answerA" : "bacteria",
                    "answerB" : "Microbe",
                    "answerC" : "amoebae"
                }
            ],
            "answer" : "b"
        },
        {
            "type" : "multi",
            "question" : "What emoji is this?",
            "emojis" : "🦠",
            "answers" : [
                {
                    "answerA" : "bacteria",
                    "answerB" : "Microbe",
                    "answerC" : "amoebae"
                }
            ],
            "answer" : "b"
        },
        {
            "type" : "multi",
            "question" : "What emoji is this?",
            "emojis" : "🤺",
            "answers" : [
                {
                    "answerA" : "person fencing",
                    "answerB" : "fencer",
                    "answerC" : "fencing sport"
                }
            ],
            "answer" : "a"
        },
        {
            "type" : "multi",
            "question" : "What emoji is this?",
            "emojis" : "🕴️",
            "answers" : [
                {
                    "answerA" : "person in suit levitating",
                    "answerB" : "man in suit levitating",
                    "answerC" : "guy in suit floating"
                }
            ],
            "answer" : "a"
        },
        {
            "type" : "text",
            "question" : "What tv series is this?",
            "emojis" : "👩‍🦲⚗️💎",
            "answers" : [
                {
                    "answerA" : "",
                    "answerB" : "",
                    "answerC" : ""
                }
            ],
            "answer" : "breaking bad"
        },
        {
            "type" : "multi",
            "question" : "What emoji is this?",
            "emojis" : "📯",
            "answers" : [
                {
                    "answerA" : "fog horn",
                    "answerB" : "post horn",
                    "answerC" : "french tuba"
                }
            ],
            "answer" : "b"
        },
        {
            "type" : "multi",
            "question" : "Which is the most used emoji?",
            "emojis" : "😂 ❤️ 💩",
            "answers" : [
                {
                    "answerA" : "😂",
                    "answerB" : "❤️",
                    "answerC" : "💩"
                }
            ],
            "answer" : "a"
        },
        {
            "type" : "text",
            "question" : "What movie is this?",
            "emojis" : "🌹🥀",
            "answers" : [
                {
                    "answerA" : "",
                    "answerB" : "",
                    "answerC" : ""
                }
            ],
            "answer" : "beauty and the beast"
        },
        {
            "type" : "radio",
            "question" : "Select emojis that released in 2019",
            "emojis" : "👅 🥴 🐕‍🦺 🧎‍♂️ 🦮",
            "answers" : [
                {
                    "answerA" : "👅",
                    "answerB" : "🥴",
                    "answerC" : "🐕‍🦺",
                    "answerD" : "🧎‍♂️",
                    "answerE" : "🦮"
                }
            ],
            "answer" : ["c", "d", "e"]
        },
        {
            "type" : "radio",
            "question" : "Select emojis that released in 2019",
            "emojis" : "☘️ 🦦 🪐 🌿 🧉",
            "answers" : [
                {
                    "answerA" : "☘️",
                    "answerB" : "🦦",
                    "answerC" : "🪐",
                    "answerD" : "🌿",
                    "answerE" : "🧉"
                }
            ],
            "answer" : ["b", "c", "e"]
        },
        {
            "type" : "radio",
            "question" : "Select emojis that released in 2019",
            "emojis" : "🧄 🧹 🦪 💅 🧶",
            "answers" : [
                {
                    "answerA" : "🧄",
                    "answerB" : "🪐",
                    "answerC" : "🦪",
                    "answerD" : "💅",
                    "answerE" : "🩸"
                }
            ],
            "answer" : ["a", "c", "e"]
        },
        {
            "type" : "radio",
            "question" : "Select emojis with bubble in their name.",
            "emojis" : "👁️‍🗨️ 🗨️ 💬 💭 🗯️",
            "answers" : [
                {
                    "answerA" : "👁️‍🗨️",
                    "answerB" : "🗨️",
                    "answerC" : "💬",
                    "answerD" : "💭",
                    "answerE" : "🗯️"
                }
            ],
            "answer" : ["a", "b", "e"]
        },
        {
            "type" : "radio",
            "question" : "Select emojis that released in 2018",
            "emojis" : "🧽 🥶 🧩 🧂 🥴",
            "answers" : [
                {
                    "answerA" : "🧽",
                    "answerB" : "🥶",
                    "answerC" : "🧩",
                    "answerD" : "🧂",
                    "answerE" : "🥴"
                }
            ],
            "answer" : ["a", "b", "c", "d", "e"]
        },
        {
            "type" : "radio",
            "question" : "Select emojis that released in 2018",
            "emojis" : "🥵 🧿 🧈 🧫 🇺🇳",
            "answers" : [
                {
                    "answerA" : "🥵",
                    "answerB" : "🧿",
                    "answerC" : "🧈",
                    "answerD" : "🧫",
                    "answerE" : "🇺🇳"
                }
            ],
            "answer" : ["a", "b", "d"]
        },
        {
            "type" : "radio",
            "question" : "Select emojis that released in 2018",
            "emojis" : "🚹 🧹 😀 💅 🧶",
            "answers" : [
                {
                    "answerA" : "🚹",
                    "answerB" : "🧹",
                    "answerC" : "😀",
                    "answerD" : "💅",
                    "answerE" : "🧶"
                }
            ],
            "answer" : ["b", "e"]
        }
    ]
}